‪JUNG-YUN'S DIARY, JIN-WOO'S DIARY
‪HYUK-JOON'S DIARY
‪Hello, everyone!
‪-Hello.
‪-Hi, everyone.
‪-How have you been?
‪-Good.
‪-My goodness.
‪-Please sit down.
‪Hold on.
‪I think this is the first time
‪we've gotten together like this.
‪-You're right.
‪-Okay.
‪Tae-hoon, you're in trouble!
‪TAE-HOON, YOU'RE IN TROUBLE
‪You're in big trouble!
‪What are you going to do?
‪By the way,
‪I need to apologize
‪to the guys in advance.
‪Just know that I'm sorry.
‪Why?
‪I'm sorry.
‪-Oh, dear.
‪-I feel particularly bad this season.
‪We prepared a Dating IQ Test today
‪and thought it'd be good
‪to do it as after service.
‪Let's begin by taking the Dating IQ Test
‪and dive into some intensive tutoring.
‪We're going to ask you some questions.
‪Write your answer on the board
‪and hold it up.
‪Then we'll have a discussion about it.
‪-Sounds good.
‪-That's what we'll do.
‪Shall we jump right in
‪and do the first question?
‪All right, then.
‪This question is for the men.
‪-Okay.
‪"Which of the following men's
‪words or actions is the worst?"
‪"Number one."
‪"Oversharing unwanted information
‪with a woman he's interested in."
‪If something flashes through your mind,
‪keep it to yourself for now.
‪You'll experience this a lot.
‪That's right.
‪-"Number two."
‪-But hold on for now.
‪"Always asking for the woman's opinion
‪and acting passive."
‪"Number three."
‪"Ignoring a letter
‪from a woman who likes him,
‪even after she told him she sent it."
‪That's so wrong.
‪"Number four."
‪-"Calling it 'fate,'
‪-Jeez, come on.
‪but still giving other women a chance."
‪-And eating chocolate with them.
‪-"Number five."
‪"Giving his matching item prize
‪to another woman."
‪"Number six. Going on a date
‪with a different ‪nuna
‪instead of the one who likes him."
‪We're in really big trouble.
‪Totally.
‪WE'RE IN REALLY BIG TROUBLE
‪Write down your answer
‪and hold it up.
‪Hold up your boards.
‪Tae-hoon, why did you choose number four?
‪4. CALLING IT FATE, BUT STILL GIVING
‪OTHER WOMEN A CHANCE
‪-Excuse me?
‪-Why is number four the worst?
‪I mean, isn't it obvious?
‪"Calling it fate, but still giving
‪other women a chance"?
‪What are your thoughts on
‪people ignoring letters?
‪I'm not sure, but I do know
‪-number four is the worst.
‪-Okay, got it.
‪He dodged that one nicely.
‪Guess he's clueless.
‪Jin-woo, why did you choose number five?
‪I think number five is the worst.
‪Why? What's your reason?
‪If you won a matching item prize,
‪you should wear it with that person.
‪It's not right to give it to someone else.
‪-I see.
‪-It's not right.
‪I want to ask the women too.
‪Which do you think is the worst?
‪For me, it has to be number four.
‪4. CALLING IT FATE, BUT STILL GIVING
‪OTHER WOMEN A CHANCE
‪-Number four.
‪-That's just unbelievable.
‪Who in the world would do that?
‪Right, I want to know too.
‪I personally think Hyun-seo's case
‪should be featured in a mystery show.
‪It would totally fit.
‪That's how bizarre her case is.
‪I didn't even get to number six.
‪I just chose number three.
‪It was an obvious choice.
‪Number three was the choice for you.
‪Tae-hoon, why are you staring
‪at the ceiling?
‪Oh, I just noticed something.
‪The next question is for the women.
‪All right, this next question
‪is for the women.
‪"Which of the following women's
‪words or actions is the worst?"
‪"Number one."
‪"Continuing to drink while clearly drunk
‪and insisting she's fine."
‪"Number two."
‪"Giving gifts to two different men
‪at the same time."
‪"Number three. Ordering someone to
‪mind their behavior
‪-during the talking stage."
‪-Who said that?
‪-Was it me?
‪-"Number four."
‪"Continually demanding
‪that someone make them smoothies."
‪You continually demanded?
‪-Blueberry smoothies.
‪-Demanding is a bit…
‪I have a feeling they were blueberry.
‪"Number five. Going on a date
‪with another man
‪after making plans to talk that evening."
‪"Number six. Saying they want to date
‪but chatting with women around the clock!"
‪The women will ask each other,
‪"Is it me or is it you?"
‪"Was that about me?"
‪It's probably hard to remember.
‪All right, please hold up your boards.
‪Look at that.
‪Soo-hyun chose number four.
‪Making smoothies isn't easy, you know.
‪-Right, it's a hassle.
‪-It is.
‪What do you want to play for?
‪Make me the same thing you made today.
‪The strawberry banana smoothie? Okay.
‪Tae-hoon's a smoothie wizard.
‪-He's a fruit expert.
‪-"Smoothie wizard."
‪But for some people,
‪that could be their way
‪to open up a conversation.
‪R…Right.
‪"R…Right."
‪-Right.
‪-It could've meant more than that.
‪That's nothing.
‪What should I say?
‪I mean, it was pretty mean.
‪So it's understandable. Got it.
‪What about you, Han-ju?
‪You chose number one.
‪Is there anything you'd like to say?
‪It's a shame.
‪I know drunk people say this all the time,
‪but I swear I'm not drunk.
‪Even you know you're lying!
‪I was determined to hold myself back
‪before I joined the show,
‪but I guess I did that
‪because I was emotionally exhausted.
‪Number three for Hyun-seo?
‪Okay, number three.
‪3. ORDERING SOMEONE TO
‪"MIND THEIR BEHAVIOR"
‪Sorry, but do you have PTSD?
‪Actually, I don't remember.
‪If you don't remember, let's replay it.
‪It was a warning, after all.
‪Mind your behavior.
‪If you use your hidden weapon
‪on a date with another woman,
‪I will rip your clothes to shreds.
‪Right there and then.
‪So Hyun-seo said,
‪"Mind your behavior."
‪"Or I'll rip your clothes to shreds."
‪-I remember.
‪-I'm sure you do.
‪-I remember now.
‪-I remember too.
‪-I totally remember.
‪-You do?
‪But that was…
‪That was just a playful joke.
‪-It was a joke?
‪-Yes.
‪Let's see here.
‪Seo-yoon chose number six.
‪Yes.
‪-Number six.
‪-Number six is…
‪You seem like someone
‪who can only be reached through Soo-hyun.
‪-Like--
‪-Really?
‪-Yeah, you're always with her.
‪-That's true.
‪I even wondered
‪if I had to ask her to get you.
‪-Hi.
‪-Is Seo-yoon with you?
‪Yeah.
‪What about you, Su-ji?
‪I chose number five.
‪"Going on a date with another man
‪after making plans to talk that evening."
‪But if you're up for it,
‪maybe sometime after the three-way date…
‪Later this evening?
‪Yeah, this evening is good.
‪Okay, sure.
‪Let's do that.
‪Is it not Jung-yun?
‪Did she choose Seung-hyun?
‪HAN SU-JI PICKED CHOI HYUK-JOON
‪At the time,
‪it just felt like
‪everyone assumed Jung-yun and I
‪were a done deal.
‪But I actually wanted to get to know
‪the other guys too.
‪I mean,
‪I knew my decision would cause a stir,
‪but I just sucked it up and hit send.
‪-I see.
‪-Good job.
‪Anyway, we spent some time
‪going over what went wrong
‪to clear the air a bit.
‪-Next question, please.
‪-Sounds good.
‪This question is for the men.
‪"Based on the following conversation,
‪what does the girlfriend want the most?"
‪"What should we eat?"
‪"Anything is fine."
‪"How about blood sausage soup?"
‪"But isn't it too hot for that?"
‪"Then what about ‪naengmyeon‪?"
‪"I get a stomachache
‪after eating cold food."
‪"How about ‪malatang‪?"
‪"But you don't really like it."
‪"Let's go for pork belly, then."
‪"Grilling pork belly is too much trouble."
‪"What about sushi?"
‪-"Sushi?"
‪-"You like sushi, right?"
‪"I had it for lunch yesterday."
‪-All right.
‪-Now then.
‪Which of the options
‪does your girlfriend want to eat?
‪My appetite is gone, but let's do this.
‪If you get this wrong, you can't date.
‪Seriously.
‪Say goodbye to dating.
‪I know this is difficult,
‪but give it a try.
‪-Try to guess.
‪-There's a correct answer.
‪Take turns guessing. Which one is it?
‪Do you know what it is?
‪-Totally.
‪-It's easy.
‪-It's too easy.
‪-It's easy?
‪Yes.
‪Okay.
‪Let's take a look at your answers.
‪The women all chose the same number.
‪Oh, so are the men…
‪He chose number four.
‪Jung-yun is the only one
‪who chose number four.
‪She says grilling it
‪is too much trouble, so--
‪-Okay, got it.
‪-Yes.
‪Moving on…
‪I can grill it, then.
‪And the rest of you
‪agree on number three?
‪I've noticed ‪malatang
‪is the magic word for women.
‪So I thought it was a safe bet.
‪-He chose based on the dish?
‪-No other reason?
‪Jae-seo, at what kind of meals
‪was ‪malatang‪ brought up?
‪With my friends.
‪I've been to Haidilao a few times.
‪-Right, you went with friends.
‪-Right.
‪-You've been there?
‪-But you don't like ‪malatang‪?
‪I see.
‪But there is a correct answer.
‪-What is it?
‪-The correct answer is…
‪-Number three.
‪Number three?
‪Number three, ‪malatang‪!
‪Most of you got it right.
‪Here's the second question for the men.
‪This one is fun.
‪"After a fun double date,
‪your girlfriend asks,
‪'Babe, isn't my friend pretty?'"
‪-I mean, she's pretty.
‪-Super pretty.
‪"Even so, please describe in sentence form
‪the best way to respond to this."
‪Seung-hyun and Hyuk-joon,
‪hurry up and write down your response.
‪Seung-hyun? Why?
‪I think I know.
‪Like, "You're prettier."
‪Or "She's pretty, but she's not my type."
‪-You nailed it.
‪-Right?
‪Are you a man?
‪-You know women.
‪-Maybe I should date women.
‪-Hold up your boards.
‪-Everyone's done, right?
‪One, two, three.
‪Q. WHAT'S YOUR RESPONSE TO
‪"ISN'T MY FRIEND PRETTY?"
‪Hold on.
‪Tae-hoon, read your answer out loud.
‪Read it out loud.
‪That's my favorite one.
‪Actually, me too.
‪"I don't remember what she looks like.
‪What was her name again?"
‪"What was her name again?" All right.
‪What do you think?
‪-Nice one.
‪-That's the best.
‪-First place.
‪-Well, I disagree.
‪-Same here.
‪What do you two think?
‪If he asks me, "What was her name again?"
‪then he'll look her up on Instagram.
‪Hey, that's sketchy!
‪-Right?
‪-I get it.
‪-He asked on purpose.
‪-I didn't think about that.
‪Jin-woo.
‪"She's pretty,
‪but she's not as pretty as you."
‪-Just telling her what she wants to hear.
‪-That's how you'd respond.
‪Hyuk-joon?
‪"Yeah, she's pretty."
‪"Yeah, she's pretty"?
‪-What do you mean?
‪-You can't help that she's pretty.
‪Right, I'm just stating a fact.
‪-I can't help it. It's the truth.
‪-Since it's the truth.
‪All right, Jae-seo.
‪"Is she, though?"
‪That's too aggressive, no?
‪-"Is she, though?"
‪-I'm not sure.
‪-But if you say this,
‪it feels like you're laying it on thick.
‪But my response is casual.
‪"Is she, though?"
‪-That's the tone.
‪-Like, "I'm not sure."
‪If you flatter her too much--
‪-It's over the top?
‪-She'll get bored.
‪-Okay.
‪-So, an indifferent "Is she, though?"
‪-"Not as much as you, dear."
‪You sound like a grandma.
‪NOT AS MUCH AS YOU, DEAR
‪"Oh goodness! Not as much as you, dear."
‪"Not a chance!"
‪"She could never compare to you!"
‪You get me, right?
‪I'm just saying the friend isn't
‪-as pretty as my girlfriend.
‪-I love it when Eun-ji reacts like this.
‪Jung-yun made this happen.
‪I guess.
‪"Not as much as you, dear."
‪But it is a romantic comment.
‪This sounds like…
‪"Gosh, I'm not sure."
‪Is that what you'll say?
‪-"I really don't know."
‪-That's how I sound?
‪That's it, right?
‪Or what if Jung-yun went,
‪"Not as much as you, dear"?
‪How about that one?
‪-I like it.
‪-It's not bad.
‪Next question, please.
‪"Which of the following
‪is a woman's favorite style
‪of flirting over drinks?"
‪"Number one, getting her ice cream
‪or some other hangover remedy."
‪"Number two, telling her to slow down
‪and keeping her from drinking too much."
‪"Number three, quietly looking out for her
‪by providing bar snacks."
‪"Number four, taking a drink for her."
‪"Number five, using spoons, chopsticks,
‪or whatever is available
‪to open bottles or mix drinks
‪to liven up the mood."
‪"Number six, patting her back
‪while she's vomiting."
‪Let's see which flirting style
‪women like the most.
‪We'll talk to the women
‪after we see your answers.
‪-Ready?
‪Please hold up your boards.
‪Three, three, one, one, and one.
‪Number three, number one.
‪Hey, they actually know a thing or two!
‪These guys aren't clueless.
‪Which one would make your heart race?
‪What kind of flirting style?
‪I'd say number two.
‪-"Slow down."
‪-Yes.
‪Number two would hurt my pride too much,
‪so that's not for me.
‪Right, Han-ju would never accept that.
‪I chose number one,
‪but asking me to go with him
‪-would be better than going himself.
‪-Right.
‪My heart would flutter
‪if he got me water instead of bar snacks.
‪I'm a lightweight, so if the guy says,
‪"Drink this and sober up."
‪I think my heart would race a bit.
‪I like a guy getting me bar snacks,
‪but with a twist.
‪Imagine there's a table here.
‪Now imagine you're me.
‪This is the type of bar snack I like.
‪The one right in front of me.
‪And then you go, "Yeah, anyway…"
‪But the main point here is…
‪This is the important part.
‪How about this instead?
‪"Here, just eat it all."
‪"It's yours. Eat it."
‪Here's what matters the most.
‪Guys, do you know what it is?
‪Looking the other way
‪and being nonchalant.
‪That's right. Be nonchalant.
‪It shouldn't be, "You like this snack,
‪so let me put this in front of you."
‪That's right.
‪-You're right.
‪-It's the best way.
‪-Here's another tough question.
‪-Okay.
‪Gosh, this one…
‪There can be multiple answers here.
‪Oh, this one is tough. Here we go.
‪"Describe all the reasons why the woman
‪got angry in the following situation."
‪"You're celebrating your girlfriend's
‪birthday and the first anniversary."
‪"At a nice restaurant, you take her hand
‪and tell her you love her."
‪"Afterward, your girlfriend says
‪she's tired, so you both go home early."
‪"The next day, your girlfriend
‪gets angry at you."
‪This one is hard.
‪He celebrated her birthday
‪and their first anniversary together.
‪He held her hand and told her
‪that he loves her.
‪They parted ways since she was tired,
‪but then she got angry?
‪Jeez, this is…
‪Is it too hard?
‪I'd be like, "Why?"
‪Maybe she just doesn't like me.
‪There's no reason for her to get mad.
‪-Are you guys ready?
‪-I don't know.
‪-Jung-yun, what did you--
‪-Jae-seo is still writing.
‪Jung-yun isn't done either.
‪I wonder what the reason could be.
‪-Tae-hoon, are you done already?
‪-I know exactly why.
‪There's only one reason.
‪-Only one?
‪-That's right.
‪But it says, "Describe all the reasons."
‪They even emphasized "all the reasons."
‪Okay.
‪All right, then.
‪Show us your answers.
‪Now then.
‪Please take turns sharing your answer.
‪"Everything was on his own damn terms"?
‪What in the world is that?
‪Okay, then.
‪Let's start with Tae-hoon.
‪"They were supposed to celebrate together,
‪but everything was on his own damn terms."
‪-My gosh.
‪-Seriously?
‪Are you kidding me?
‪He didn't understand the question.
‪Okay, explain it again.
‪What made you say that?
‪It says in the first line
‪they were supposed to celebrate together,
‪but he told her
‪he loves her without asking.
‪And when she said she was tired,
‪he sent her off.
‪I think that's why she was angry.
‪-That's what you think?
‪-Yes.
‪-Everything was on his terms.
‪-Okay.
‪I guess you could see it that way.
‪Jin-woo says, "He combined
‪her birthday and their anniversary."
‪"He sent her home early
‪when she said she was tired."
‪Oh, I see.
‪-I get it now.
‪-What do you mean by "combined"?
‪It says they celebrated
‪the two events together,
‪but I think it's a problem
‪if that was his own decision.
‪Even if they had agreed on this,
‪he should've at least
‪gotten her a separate gift.
‪-Terrific answer.
‪-Gosh.
‪-Wow.
‪-He's so good.
‪That never occurred to you, right?
‪I had no idea what was wrong
‪with that situation.
‪But I can see it now.
‪Yeah, something even I missed.
‪Hyuk-joon?
‪I was focused
‪on the "nice restaurant" part.
‪If you hold her hand there,
‪she won't like it.
‪And saying "I love you" on top of that
‪comes across as an attention seeker.
‪You can do all that in private.
‪Have you noticed
‪they're completely off base?
‪But doesn't that mean
‪she just doesn't like you?
‪No, that's not it.
‪I think she might not like it.
‪Okay, Jae-seo wrote up a whole report.
‪I wrote down four reasons.
‪First, you should check if the anniversary
‪and birthday fall on the same day.
‪If the dates are different, it's better
‪to celebrate them separately.
‪If they fall on the same day,
‪the celebration needs to be
‪at least twice as big.
‪-They need to be a bit separated?
‪-Yes.
‪Or if you're going to combine them,
‪step up the celebration and make it big.
‪Second, saying you love someone
‪is what you do on a normal day anyway.
‪But it's a special occasion.
‪These two things
‪need to be differentiated.
‪-Separate celebration and love?
‪-Wait, hold on.
‪What are you talking about?
‪You need to differentiate
‪celebration from love.
‪All right, then.
‪After you say, "I love you,"
‪then you say, "Happy birthday."
‪He's saying to keep them separate.
‪Keep them separate?
‪-There should be an order of sorts.
‪-You're right.
‪There needs to be an order of events.
‪They need to be nuanced differently.
‪So the "I love you" part
‪should come later.
‪Maybe say it when you part ways.
‪-Celebration comes first.
‪-Yes.
‪That's so funny.
‪I didn't even think about that.
‪-Seriously.
‪-If she says she's tired,
‪you should take her home
‪unless she lives really far away.
‪-Take her home.
‪-Right.
‪He should've done that.
‪Then she got angry the next day.
‪In my opinion,
‪if you sense there's a problem,
‪you need to ask right away
‪if you did something wrong.
‪Jeez, you created a response manual.
‪At least one of these
‪should be right.
‪You know, they all sound
‪convincing but wrong.
‪My first thought was
‪maybe the restaurant
‪didn't serve good food.
‪-She didn't like it?
‪-Food is important.
‪Maybe the dishes weren't tasty.
‪And she may have been tired,
‪but she probably wanted to be together.
‪But they parted ways early.
‪Being tired and wanting to be together…
‪I thought since it was a special day,
‪they shouldn't have parted ways early.
‪He should've done something
‪to help her feel less tired.
‪-He should've thought of something.
‪-Yes.
‪Seo-yoon, what do you think?
‪It's their first anniversary,
‪but he only held her hand.
‪-Wow.
‪-That is a big problem, indeed.
‪"It's their first anniversary,
‪but he only held her hand."
‪That was the response
‪from one of our eternal singles.
‪This is huge progress.
‪-What an adult.
‪-Nice.
‪Everyone, there are actually four reasons
‪why the woman got angry.
‪-Why?
‪-"Number one."
‪"He combined her birthday
‪and their anniversary."
‪"Number two. He said he loves her
‪without getting her a gift."
‪Hey, that's a bit much.
‪Come on, not even a birthday gift?
‪Jeez.
‪Well, he might be broke.
‪Then that's okay.
‪"Number three. He went home for real
‪when she said she was tired."
‪"Number four."
‪"He got home and didn't message her
‪until the next morning."
‪-He didn't even tell her he got home okay.
‪-Let's see.
‪Jae-seo guessed almost everything right.
‪When it comes to these questions…
‪the more you write, the better.
‪Hyuk-joon missed all of them.
‪Hyuk-joon surprisingly
‪didn't get any correct.
‪Okay, then.
‪Next question, please.
‪"Which of the following men
‪has the least interest in me?"
‪"He avoids eye contact with me."
‪"He responds to messages,
‪but he won't reach out first."
‪"He talks the loudest
‪when we're with friends."
‪"He says he'll set me up on a blind date."
‪All of them sound bad.
‪But there's a correct answer, right?
‪-Yes.
‪-There is? Okay.
‪Let's take a look.
‪One, two, three.
‪Q. WHICH MAN
‪IS THE LEAST INTERESTED IN ME?
‪Oh, they're divided.
‪Four people chose number two,
‪and two people chose number four.
‪Telling me to go on a blind date
‪feels like he's saying,
‪"Date someone else."
‪-That's why I chose number four.
‪-Okay.
‪Su-ji, why did you choose number two?
‪So I have to message him first
‪to get a response.
‪That'd make me look desperate.
‪-Like I'm the only one making an effort.
‪-Right.
‪I agree.
‪What do you think, Hyuk-joon?
‪I think it's number four.
‪Why?
‪4. THE MAN WHO WANTS TO
‪SET ME UP ON A BLIND DATE
‪Because I think he's drawing a line
‪and leaving no hope whatsoever.
‪-But he's giving her a chance.
‪-"A chance"?
‪"A chance"?
‪Mr. Give-Them-a-Chance.
‪He loves giving chances.
‪What about you, Jae-seo?
‪Do you think it's number four?
‪I think it's number two.
‪-Number two.
‪-Why?
‪You tend to do everything
‪to reach out first.
‪-If you like someone?
‪-Yes.
‪-You'll even make up an excuse.
‪-That's so true.
‪All right, the answer is…
‪There's a correct answer.
‪Number two is the answer.
‪Yay!
‪-Amazing.
‪-So here's why.
‪I think people in general,
‪not just men,
‪will reach out first
‪if they really like someone.
‪-Right.
‪-I'm talking from experience.
‪So no one likes testing people?
‪I think it could actually be cute.
‪"Want to go on a blind date?"
‪"Why? Because you like me?"
‪I sound like a nosy aunt,
‪sitting around the eternal singles.
‪It's like, "Not as much as you, dear."
‪"Not as much as you, dear."
‪All right.
‪This question is for the women.
‪"There's a guy I talk to every day.
‪We even hold hands when we meet up."
‪"I want him to admit he likes me.
‪What should I say to get him to confess?"
‪How in the world do you do that?
‪Get him to confess…
‪Wait, get him to confess?
‪Well…
‪Give it a try
‪and write down your answer.
‪Getting someone
‪to confess their feelings is hard.
‪Shall we take a look
‪at the answers for now?
‪Please hold up your boards.
‪I LIKE YOU
‪HOW ABOUT YOU?
‪-These answers show their personalities.
‪-Hey, Su-ji.
‪I JUST ASK HIM TO BE MY BOYFRIEND
‪"TOMORROW WILL BE OUR OFFICIAL FIRST DATE"
‪I can see your personalities.
‪Take a look at this here.
‪This is what always made me sad.
‪-He's right.
‪-Why?
‪What are you talking about?
‪You're attractive.
‪-Because he isn't swayed?
‪-"Am I unattractive to you?"
‪That's very straightforward.
‪-Su-ji just finished writing her answer.
‪-Yay!
‪"If you want to keep holding my hand,
‪ask me to be your girlfriend first."
‪-That's right.
‪-Totally.
‪Be official first, then hold hands.
‪Seo-yoon, why did you…
‪-"Huh? Why are you holding my hand?"
‪-"Why are you holding my hand?"
‪"Huh? Why are you holding my hand?"
‪"Why are you holding my hand?"
‪That's totally her.
‪It sounds just like her.
‪"Why are you holding my hand?"
‪That's right.
‪It's weird to hold hands
‪if you're not dating him.
‪Guys, do any of these answers
‪make you want to confess your feelings?
‪I like Seo-yoon's response.
‪"Why are you holding my hand?"
‪That question makes you
‪want to ask her out?
‪It'll give me a chance to explain
‪why I'm holding her hand.
‪-It can give you a little push.
‪-I see.
‪Jin-woo?
‪I think Hyun-seo's
‪and Jeong-eun's answers are the best.
‪They help you confess?
‪The question here is
‪what'll make me ask her out, so…
‪Something like this
‪actually happened to me.
‪I met a guy about five times
‪over the course of a month.
‪I just waited passively
‪and ended up getting dumped.
‪I don't know what to say
‪because I already got it wrong before.
‪Right.
‪You're not sure what to do
‪because of this experience.
‪What would you say, Eun-ji?
‪Me? I've thought of a few different ways.
‪The first is…
‪I'll use Seung-hyun as an example.
‪"Hey, Seung-hyun."
‪"Seo-yoon told me she thought
‪you and I are dating."
‪She's an expert.
‪If he says we're not, that's it.
‪Here's the second way.
‪Let's assume Seung-hyun wants
‪to ask me to be his girlfriend today.
‪As we're walking,
‪"Seung-hyun, I know
‪you want to ask me something."
‪"And my answer is 'yes.'"
‪"Oh, really?"
‪"You can lend me money?"
‪"Gosh, thanks so much."
‪"Seriously."
‪"I really hesitated because you switched
‪agencies only recently."
‪You need to really read the room, though.
‪Check and make sure.
‪"Gosh, I'm so relieved."
‪Don't forget to make sure.
‪That's hilarious.
‪So this actually happened to me.
‪We have been seeing each other, but he
‪wouldn't ask me to be his girlfriend.
‪Then the guy asked me,
‪"Why aren't you dating anyone?"
‪-So when that happened--
‪-Was he testing you?
‪When he asked why I wasn't dating,
‪I went, "Me?"
‪"Because you're the one I like."
‪"Oh, really?"
‪"But the feeling isn't mutual."
‪-"Gosh."
‪-Wait a minute.
‪What a bad guy.
‪That's so mean.
‪-All right.
‪-So now,
‪we've finished answering
‪all the Dating IQ Test questions.
‪Did you have fun?
‪-Yes.
‪That's good to hear.
‪We will now announce
‪the MVP eternal single.
‪The MVP eternal single will receive
‪a matching wine glass set,
‪courtesy of Netflix.
‪-Wow, a set?
‪-And…
‪-Date funds.
‪-Is that cash?
‪They get date funds.
‪-That's crazy.
‪-You even get date funds.
‪Wow.
‪You'll even receive date funds.
‪Please announce the MVP.
‪I will now call out the MVP.
‪The MVP of the day.
‪The person who will get the wine glass set
‪and 500,000 won in date funds is…
‪Yoon Jung-yun.
‪MVP ETERNAL SINGLE
‪YOON JUNG-YUN
‪Congratulations.
‪-I'm so jealous.
‪-Good for you.
‪-Wow.
‪-A trophy!
‪-What's that?
‪What's that?
‪"MVP eternal single, Yoon Jung-yun."
‪"This award goes to the above person
‪in recognition of proving to be
‪the best eternal single."
‪-Here you go.
‪-Thank you.
‪-Good for you.
‪-Is this a good thing?
‪No, of course not.
‪It's okay. You can start
‪your next chapter now.
‪That's right.
‪Well,
‪it looks like I became
‪the top eternal single.
‪I know better than anyone
‪that I'm clumsy and inexperienced,
‪but I hope everyone
‪will look kindly on me.
‪I also hope to meet someone
‪who can be patient with me.
‪Very nice.
‪We'll always support your dreams
‪and journey to find love.
‪Thank you for today, everyone!
‪-Thank you!
‪Thank you!
‪Are we taking a group photo?
‪Come on, gather around.
‪-Okay.
‪After participating in this show,
‪it made me reflect on my life.
‪I lacked in many ways,
‪but that made it more authentic.
‪There were things I did wrong,
‪and things I wish I'd done differently.
‪After all, none of us are used to dating.
‪I really want to become a better person
‪and successfully date someone.
‪I experienced so many emotions
‪over those ten days.
‪It was a new experience
‪that helped me learn more about myself.
‪I took a leap of faith
‪and just went for it,
‪and I found that it was no big deal
‪and totally manageable.
‪I thought it wasn't obvious
‪that I was an eternal single,
‪but this show helped me realize
‪why I am an eternal single.
‪This experience helped me grow a lot
‪and learn a great deal,
‪especially after receiving
‪this after service.
‪I'll definitely try
‪to date someone this year.
‪Thank you.
‪Ready? One, two, three!
‪Subtitle translation by:
‪Jenny Kim